<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>rust on My Programming Blog</title>
    <link>https://shaneutt.com/categories/rust/</link>
    <description>Recent content in rust on My Programming Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 18:57:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shaneutt.com/categories/rust/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rust - Fast &#43; Small Docker Image Builds</title>
      <link>https://shaneutt.com/blog/rust-fast-small-docker-image-builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 18:57:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shaneutt.com/blog/rust-fast-small-docker-image-builds/</guid>
      <description>Fast + Small Docker Image Builds for Rust Apps In this post I&amp;rsquo;m going to demonstrate how to create small, quickly built Docker Images for Rust applications.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start by creating a simple test application, and then building and iterating on a Dockerfile.
Requirements Ensure you have the following installed:
 rustup v1.14.0+ docker v17.06.2+  Setup: demo app setup Make sure you have and are using the latest stable Rust with rustup:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming - Deploying Rust Webapps on Kubernetes on DC/OS using Skaffold</title>
      <link>https://shaneutt.com/blog/rust-k8s-skaffold-dcos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 12:50:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shaneutt.com/blog/rust-k8s-skaffold-dcos/</guid>
      <description>Deploying Rust Webapps on Kubernetes on DC/OS using Skaffold Since my last post I&amp;rsquo;ve joined as an engineer at Mesosphere and have been developing data pipeline software for cluster diagnostics.
During this same time I&amp;rsquo;ve been deploying the software I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on using Kubernetes on DC/OS, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been keeping up my interest in the Rust, so I put together a demo of deploying webapps in Rust to Kubernetes on DC/OS using Skaffold:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rust - Coveralls.io for Rust</title>
      <link>https://shaneutt.com/blog/rust-coveralls-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 14:30:44 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shaneutt.com/blog/rust-coveralls-2017/</guid>
      <description>While looking for a way to provide code coverage with https://coveralls.iofor Rust, I stumbled upon a solution while reading through Iron.
The solution involves a tool called kcovwhich is a Linux/OSX code coverage tester for compiled languages.
This tool can be implemented inside a .travis.ymlfile to push coverage data from a Travis CI build.
Here is an example .travis.yml file:
Basically all you have to do is run:
Changing &amp;ldquo;riak-*&amp;rdquo; for your own project, and everything before that is just to compiled kcov inside the Travis CI environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rust - std::convert::Into and std::convert::From</title>
      <link>https://shaneutt.com/blog/rust-convert-into-and-from-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 14:34:10 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shaneutt.com/blog/rust-convert-into-and-from-2017/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been spending time recently learning the Rust Programming Languageby writing a Riak Clientusing Riak&amp;rsquo;s Protocol Buffers API.
Through Ownership&amp;amp; BorrowingRust enables safety that generally comes at the cost of flexibility. Through features like TraitsRust is able to give some flexibility back to the programmer.
Some traits I&amp;rsquo;ve started to use recently include std::convert::Intoand std::convert::From.
When the Into trait is applied to a type, it allows it to consume itself to convert to another type.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>